givemegay.com 2014-03-27

# GiveMeGay: Free Gay Porn & Gay Sex Videos

**Last revised 30 January 2013**

Gamma Entertainment Inc is the owner and operator of GiveMeGay.com and shall be known in this Privacy Policy as "We", "Us" and "Our". We understand that User privacy is very important and therefore have set out information which explains what information is collected from You ("User", "Your") and how it is used. 

Only adults who are at least 18 years old (21 years old in some jurisdictions) may navigate, sign up to become a member or use GiveMeGay.com. All persons under this age must leave the site immediately.

WHAT IS COLLECTED

By navigating the site or communicating with the customer service department, We collect personal information provided such as email address, IP, browser and other anonymous demographic information. If Users send personal correspondence via email, ticket or chat, such information will be maintained as a record of correspondence.

COOKIES

Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored on the computer or device used to access and surf websites for future access. GiveMeGay.com uses cookies which are essential to the operation of the site in order for Users to view the content. Other cookies that may be used include analytical cookies which monitor the performance of GiveMeGay.com and help Us provide better products or identify areas that need maintenance. Tracking cookies are used in relation to those who help promote GiveMeGay.com. Functional cookies are helpful to record Your preferences when You return to GiveMeGay.com.com; for example, they are used to remember the scenes or photos You store in Your favorites folder. Finally, advertising cookies or third party cookies may be used to provide specific advertising to Users which We believe are relevant to Your interests. Please note that We cannot control cookies placed on your computer or device by third party advertisers

HOW TO CONTROL COOKIES

Users are not obligated to accept cookies and Your browser can be modified to refuse cookies. You can also delete cookies You may already have. Should You choose to refuse all cookies, many websites may not function properly, including Ours. It is possible to modify Your browser settings to only accept cookies with Your consent before each cookie is placed on Your computer or device to give You more control over what is placed on Your computer or device, however it may slow down Your experience on the web.

CONSENT

Users should enjoy the full experience of GiveMeGay.com. By the continued use and browsing of GiveMeGay.com You are consenting to Our processing of Your personal information, communicating with You and analysis of the information You provide.

SECURITY

We take reasonable precautions to maintain security of any information obtained from and about Users, and to protect against the loss, misuse and alterations of information under Our control. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to GiveMeGay.com and you do so at your own risk.

HOW INFORMATION IS USED

All information collected is used to facilitate viewing of content and features at GiveMeGay.com. We may use the information collected to improve marketing, analyse site usage, improve content offerings, customize site layout and provide information about GiveMeGay.com to its Users. We are constantly striving to deliver the best to Users and We may use the information collected to deliver information targeted to User interests. Such information may be sold, shared, licensed or rented out to our partners, affiliated or unaffiliated third party web service providers who display banners or links on GiveMeGay.com. We encourage Users to read their policies, terms and conditions as they are not the same as Ours.

SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

We may disclose personal information collected if required by law, court order or other governmental authority or when We believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of GiveMeGay.com.

In the event of a change of ownership (merger, acquisition, sale of assets) We reserve the right to transfer all User information collected in connection with GiveMeGay.com to such separate entity.

LEGAL

This policy does not apply to any linked website to GiveMeGay.com. Please consult the privacy policy, terms and conditions of the website to which the redirection may occur if clicking on a banner or advertisement.

By using/navigating GiveMeGay.com Users acknowledge they have read, understood and agree to be bound by this privacy policy, the terms and conditions of GiveMeGay.com

Feel free to contact Us at Gamma Entertainment Inc, 3300 Boulevard Cote Vertu, Suite 406, Montreal, QC, H4R 2B7, Canada. support@givemegay.com
